# CONTACT

Phone

+1 (608) 630 6650

**Email** 

Shawn.W.Nha@gmail.com

Location

Seattle, Washington

LinkedIn

linkedin.com/in/ShawnNha

**GitHub** 

github.com/ShawnWNha

# SKILL SET

**Languages:** Python, JavaScript, C#, Java

Front-End: HTML5, CSS3, jQuery, AJAX

Frameworks: Django, Flask, Angular.js,

Node.js / Express.js,

ASP.NET Core.

Dapper/Entity

**Databases:** SQL (MySQL, SQLite, PostgreSQL)

NoSQL (Mongoose/MongoDB)

Version Control: Git, GitHub

Methodologies: OOP, ORM, MVC/MTV

Architecture, CRUD,

**RESTful API** 

Cloud Platforms: AWS, Azure

# **EXTRA SKILL**

Bilingual in Korean and English

# SHAWN NHA Software Engineer

Software engineer, with knowledge of Python, JavaScript and C#. With over two years of business analysis and military operations, built strong leadership and problem-solving skills. As a passionate developer, translates ideas fast into synthesized application functionalities. Possesses a strong work ethic

# **PROJECTS**

- Mapp: Map based web application with the main feature of sharing and displaying locational messages on a global map. Created a user space with login, registration, and corresponding validations. Used Angular6 to feature different routings without refreshing the page and secured invalid routing and server access with authority guard. Used-tech: Angular6, Node.js, Express.js, MongoDB, Angular Google Map, Auth Guard, ¡Query.
- Appoint: Web application to solve the time complexity in making medical appointments. Using a RESTful architecture to create a dashboard and a message board, which provides "one-click" appointments to doctors with a brief message of symptoms. Used-tech: Django2.0, MySQL server, HTML5, CSS3.

### WORK EXPERIENCE

# **Support Coordinator**

October 2017 - February 2018

# Robert Half Staffing & AppleOne Staffing, Seattle, Washington

- Designed 5 marketing surveys and processed into business models
- Utilized over 4000 rough surveys into collectable data
- Managed client specific services in response to RFIs and RFPs

# **Property Manager**

- MonVerre Property Management, Seoul, South Korea Managed 13 tenant accounts and public relations
- Extended 5 annual contracts, generating revenue \$150,000+
- Designed a web advertisement and optimized search engine

# Sergeant/Squad Commander

March 2013 - December 2014

May 2017 - September 2017

**213 Regiment Intelligence Division** 

#### Intern Analyst

June 2011 - August 2011

#### The Korea Times, Seoul, South Korea

- Conducted a research on subscriber models and compiled into business data
- Promoted "Miss Korea 2011," through top Korean search engines.
- Monitored public responses and developed analysis on a weekly basis

# **EDUCATION**

#### Certificate of Achievement

March 2018 - July 2018

# Coding Dojo, Bellevue, WA

- Completed intensive web development program, working over 1000 hours
- Achieved triple Blackbelts scoring over 95% in comprehensive exams

# Bachelor of Arts in Economics & Entrepreneurship

2010 - 2017

- University of Wisconsin-Madison, Madison, WI
- Dean's List Fall 2016 Spring 2017
- GPA (3.89/4.00)
- Vice President of Korean Entrepreneurs Organization